Hello hello meet me again Suryo
on the channel Suryo Nugroho dot id
[Music]
yes But this time we will sleepy
syncrotec health insurance
owned by Manulife namely naik
Ultimate headset Well now we will
Unbox the Jit class first yes because
there are 4 classes 3 MI Ultimate hacker
this Jit class is the
most affordable class for those with a low budget
it but don't be mistaken even though love
but this product is very powerful
with premiums starting from 400 thousand
per month you can get the
following benefits the first Jit class
has a room class of 500,000 or
double standard rukna Does that mean it's
not the price of a hotel room Yes but this
is the price of a class in a hospital for
customers who choose this Jit class if they
have to be hospitalized in a hospital can
choose any class but with a
maximum limit of 500,000 or double
standard room whichever is higher
for example if in city X and in the
hospital ah has kaf3 the price is
300,000 has 2 of them the price is 400,000 and
keras One price  500,000 then the customer
can choose first class in city x next
another example if in city y and in
hospital B has plastic price 500,000
class 2 price 650,000 and double
standard room class One price one
million with your site truck then in city
y the customer can choose one of the two with
Hi jarles standard room even though the
class price is because 650,000 is above the
class price of the cat room because the design of the
customer can choose which is
higher the second class Jit
has the on Bell feature Well is ondel
pantun is all hospital costs
will be covered by insurance
especially Manulife insurance in
this case covered
100% But there is a condition one nerve
the condition is the room class must be in accordance
with the benefits So all
hospital costs will be paid in full by
the manual if the customer chooses the class price
because in the hospital it costs 500 thousand
rupiah per day or double standard
room which is higher the third
class Jit can be used in Indonesia
and Malaysia loyal with the
same limit Hi interesting isn't it so if
the customer wants to get a second opinion
from an alternative doctor and wants to go
to Malaysia or pen this facility can
used for Yansen's hospitalization,
this facility project is finished even though
it is the class that is most talkative
But we still get a health card now
What is catechesis So if we are
treated and hospitalized at a
partner hospital, we only show
this card to the hospital and
the hospital will immediately know
the benefits and class of room we have
now interesting health insurance product
ride this Ultimate Soccer planchet
So if you have further questions,
you can directly WhatsApp me to
my number 0812345678 and all Nugroho
84@gmail.com I serve suggestions but
for purchasing life insurance policies,
health insurance, critical illness insurance
and insurance sold by
Manulife if you have further questions,
contact me at
8501 because don't forget Click the
subscribe button and like this video for
my next videos